<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smart Home on SCL Blog</title>
    <link>https://silocitylabs.com/tags/smart-home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Smart Home on SCL Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://silocitylabs.com/tags/smart-home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Filament Dryer PCB</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2025/esp32-oem-dryer-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2025/esp32-oem-dryer-box/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to take your &lt;strong&gt;Filament Dryer&lt;/strong&gt; to the next level? The &lt;strong&gt;Filament Dryer PCB&lt;/strong&gt; is the ultimate upgrade, adding enhanced &lt;strong&gt;filament material support&lt;/strong&gt;, a &lt;strong&gt;better display&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;smart home integration&lt;/strong&gt; to ensure your 3D printing workflow is seamless and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Home Upgrades with ESP32 and ESPHome</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2024/everything-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2024/everything-smart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7&#34; data-src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2024/technology-reanimated.webp&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Silocity Labs&lt;/strong&gt;, we’ve always loved exploring innovative technology and making the world of electronics more accessible. Recently, we’ve opened a new shop featuring some of our favorite creations: &lt;strong&gt;ESPHome-compatible smart devices&lt;/strong&gt; built on the powerful ESP32 platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurturing Your Garden the Smart Way</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2023/2023-10-28-esp32-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2023/2023-10-28-esp32-garden/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world of electronics and software, innovation knows no bounds. As a senior software engineer in Amherst, NY, I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved to tinker with the latest technologies to create fun and exciting projects. One such project that I recently embarked on is an automated watering system that integrates seamlessly with Home Assistant, using sensors, Tasmota, MQTT, and an ESP32 4CH relay control board. In this article, I will guide you through the process of building your own automated watering system, step by step. Please note that having a basic understanding of Home Assistant and microcontrollers is recommended to follow this guide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>433MHZ More Things for Smart Things</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/02/05/433mhz-more-things-for-smart-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 22:30:22 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/02/05/433mhz-more-things-for-smart-things/</guid>
      <description>Finally - off the breadboard and into a working environment. It&amp;rsquo;s currently working for 433mhz sensors, I will possibly be adding more frequencies later. For now I will continue refining the code to release it on github.&#xA;Day 1:&#xA;A few issues. I accidentally flipped the polarities on the siren. I will eventually implement a 12v regulator to up the voltage for the siren for the full 120db power.&#xA;Day 2:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>433mhz testing</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/19/433mhz-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 14:43:55 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/19/433mhz-testing/</guid>
      <description>I decided due to the lack of community support I am not going to make a Zigbee 433mhz chip instead I will continue my efforts with the WiFi esp8266. Now that I have the 433mhz working with the esp8266 I will be performing some distance testing with a few receivers I purchased and different antennas I have.&#xA;Update to: https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/01/smart-things-433mhz/</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete Smart Home Setup</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/28/complete-smart-home-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 18:00:51 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/28/complete-smart-home-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img class=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7&#34; data-src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/smart-home-2769210_960_720-e1514497002881.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to talk about my smart home setup from the ground up. I have many articles describing my setup in pieces but not everyone gets an entire overview of everything I have setup here. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a mansion or anything fancy like built in sprinkler/irrigation, so this will be more catered to your average city home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Assistant&lt;/strong&gt;:&#xA;r&#xA;Google Home and/or Mini manage my random routines that aren&amp;rsquo;t part of a automation rule. Going to the basement to do laundry, or going to sleep at random times. I can just send a command and google home will handle it. Link your SmartThings account and Google Home together for best results. Give all your devices aliases to make it easier to command via Google. I want one located in every central room of the house, Kitchen, Living room, Master Bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;img class=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7&#34; data-src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/100417-google-home-mini7347-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Control Center&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What controls my entire setup and why I chose this hub vs others. My only hub is a &lt;strong&gt;Samsung SmartThings hub&lt;/strong&gt;. This manages just about everything in my home minus the security cameras. I did heavy research on many hubs including Wink, IOT (hub-less), and Phillips hue. Why SmartThings?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartThings zigbee vs Dome light cover</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/26/smartthings-zigbee-vs-dome-light-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 17:55:48 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/26/smartthings-zigbee-vs-dome-light-cover/</guid>
      <description>For Christmas my mother got a full smart home kit. Samsung SmartThings, sengled bulbs, google home. After pluging everything in the hub was having issues. Finding all bulbs in dome covers. I removed the glass from the dome cover and tried again with no luck. Afterwards I removed the bulb from the socket and put it in a lamp. Detected and added to smartthings fine in the lamp. Readded it to the dome cover and it works now!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartThings &#43; Vision Micro Switch [Update]</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/18/smartthings-vision-micro-switch-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 20:17:07 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/18/smartthings-vision-micro-switch-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How to get a cheap smart home that actually works. Vision Micro switches lets you use the old fashion switch and also continue to use your old bulbs. Instead of paying $10-30 per smart bulb, you pay around $25 for a single or $30 for a 2 relay switch. 2 relay switches help you save a ton more money, you can use one for 2 gang boxes saving you 2x more money ($15/switch). If you think about it, most ceiling lights have 2-3 bulbs, Why buy so many bulbs when you can buy a single switch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/397hvxAjlj4&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartThings &#43; Vision Micro Switch</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/smartthings-vision-micro-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 19:45:08 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/smartthings-vision-micro-switch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have found a neat little alternative to full price switches online. I gave myself a budget of $20 per wall switch for the house and until I found something around that I was not gonna buy any. I just think that $50 for a wall switch is a little ridiculous in my opinion. These switches are still over my max budget but at least I found a reason for one of the partners here to buy it instead [&lt;a href=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/post/author/bana0615/&#34;&gt;bana0615&lt;/a&gt;]. He has a double switch in his house and they do not sell double smart switches anywhere. This micro controller solves his problem. The double switch relays will put me under budget for some locations in the house though with the ability to work for two switches at once.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;img class=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///yH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAABAAEAAAIBRAA7&#34; data-src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/419E0PAR7HL.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Double Toggle Switch&#34;/&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
