<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seo on SCL Blog</title>
    <link>https://silocitylabs.com/tags/seo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in seo on SCL Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 22:36:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://silocitylabs.com/tags/seo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Silocitylabs Blog</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;
            &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/luis-portfolio/blog.png&#34; alt=&#34;Blog website&#34; height=&#34;940&#34; width=&#34;1354&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
            &lt;figcaption&gt;The blog when this article was written.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
        &lt;/figure&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;The Issue:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previously on Wordpress we started noticing performance issues early on into the websites time on the web. Wordpress unfortunately is not very good with performance on high traffic websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Solution:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We decided to try out a static site generator called hugo. After migrating we noticed extreme performance improvements. We made some more adjustments while the project was hot and decided to host on github public repo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATTO.com Domain Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com-acquisition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com-acquisition/</guid>
      <description>After hearing that they have been trying to contact a company for the purchase of atto.com for 16 years, I figured I could give it a shot. I helped ATTO Technology locate the correct point of contact in a +10000 employee company to initiate negotiations of the acquisition for the 4 letter domain name. We acquired the Domain name by the end of July.
You can checkout the other contributors for refferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATTO Technology SEO Redesign</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was hired for this company to perform SEO, shortly after google had scheduled the release of a new search algorithm that would reduce views on pages that were not mobile complaint. ATTO got the effect of this with a 50% drop in traffic in a matter of days. A website with over a million views a month it needed to be overhauled. I was tasked with a complete redesign on the website and its 800+ pages. I monitored and improved SEO on the pages over time as well as slowly gained back that 50% loss in traffic. You can checkout the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ldrrp/detail/project/945228877/contributors/&#34;&gt;other contributors&lt;/a&gt; for refferences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>