<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ESP32 on SCL Blog</title>
    <link>https://silocitylabs.com/tags/esp32/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ESP32 on SCL Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://silocitylabs.com/tags/esp32/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Smart Home Devices with ESP32 and ESPHome</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2024/everything-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2024/everything-smart/</guid>
      <description>At Silocity Labs, we’ve always loved exploring innovative technology and making the world of electronics more accessible. Recently, we’ve opened a new shop featuring some of our favorite creations: ESPHome-compatible smart devices built on the powerful ESP32 platform.&#xA;This isn’t just another project for us—it’s something we enjoy doing. By turning “dumb” and outdated tech into versatile, open firmware devices, we’re making it easier for people to enjoy smart functionality without the headaches of app lock-ins, cloud dependency, or forced subscriptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurturing Your Garden the Smart Way</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2023/2023-10-28-esp32-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2023/2023-10-28-esp32-garden/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of electronics and software, innovation knows no bounds. As a senior software engineer in Amherst, NY, I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved to tinker with the latest technologies to create fun and exciting projects. One such project that I recently embarked on is an automated watering system that integrates seamlessly with Home Assistant, using sensors, Tasmota, MQTT, and an ESP32 4CH relay control board. In this article, I will guide you through the process of building your own automated watering system, step by step.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
