<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luis Rodriguez on SCL Blog</title>
    <link>https://silocitylabs.com/author/luis-rodriguez/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Luis Rodriguez on SCL Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:57:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://silocitylabs.com/author/luis-rodriguez/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn an Old Raspberry pi into an offsite backup</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2020/02/07/raspberry-pi-encrypted-offsite-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2020/02/07/raspberry-pi-encrypted-offsite-backups/</guid>
      <description>Why? Lets start off with a few notes about how and why I would do this. I already have a fireproof/waterproof drive in my house. Sounds like im all set right? Not really.
Although im set on a disaster level there are a few things that can be an issue with onsite backups. Especially with my drive being plugged in all the time.
 Theft, Although it is &amp;ldquo;theft resistant&amp;rdquo; the metal they want me to bolt down isnt very strong at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arm 64bit vs Xeon x86_64 performance on AWS</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/10/16/arm-vs-xeon-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/10/16/arm-vs-xeon-aws/</guid>
      <description>The reason for this test was to determine if arm was a viable option on aws. I noticed that arm had higher network throughputs and faster disk speeds on the aws pages. So I decided I would compare their performance using golang tests. The entire test cost me $0.68 using a quick spot instance.
The comparison was done on two very similar instances of aws servers. On paper they would almost seem to function the same but arm was just a few cents more, but lets take a look on how they performed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing nano text editor on Android</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/09/26/installing-nano-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/09/26/installing-nano-android/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a while of playing around with my build.prop file in Android I needed a way to edit faster using a text editor via adb shell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found a way using a couple of online sources to get it going. You will need to be on a rooted device.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opt out of spectrum SPAM</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/09/26/opt-out-of-spectrum-spam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/09/26/opt-out-of-spectrum-spam/</guid>
      <description>Recently I discovered a way to opt out of all spectrum spam mail, calls, door to door salesmen. I have filled out the form and will wait patiently for my spam to stop. Hopefully my mailbox will be empty in the coming weeks.
To opt out of all spam online, mail etc just click the link below:
Opt Out Spectrum Spam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Monitor and Restart in Golang</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/2019/08/14/quick-monitor-restart-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/2019/08/14/quick-monitor-restart-golang/</guid>
      <description>Go Applications On my desktop I was running a processing script that would occasionally hang at high CPU, so I wrote a quick script to monitor it and restart it. You can see it below and change it as needed.
Run it like so after compiling to a binary
nohup ./restart &amp;amp; The code
package main import ( &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; &amp;#34;io/ioutil&amp;#34; &amp;#34;log&amp;#34; &amp;#34;os/exec&amp;#34; &amp;#34;runtime&amp;#34; &amp;#34;strconv&amp;#34; &amp;#34;strings&amp;#34; &amp;#34;time&amp;#34; ) func getCPUSample() (idle, total uint64) { contents, err := ioutil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kafka Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/kafka-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 08:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/kafka-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Throughout my time working with kafka I have developed great software to use with it. But while the software did many things there are other things I still resorted to this cheat sheet for. I have put together this list of commands which I will keep updated here as I find new links and commands that help. My kafka installtion was under &lt;code&gt;/opt/kafka&lt;/code&gt; and you will need to change this to your path you installed kafka too. You can also create a symlink and just copy paste commands as they are after changing ip&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geo Location Micro API Service</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/geo-api-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/geo-api-service/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A micro api drop in service written in golang, Designed to quickly integrate into any system for any project. Uses very little resources and can handle millions of requests per second. The entire projects &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/SiloCityLabs/geo.bntech.io&#34;&gt;source code&lt;/a&gt; is posted on github.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can include a package written for Golang projects to quickly get started with a simple function.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang IP Formatting Package</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/ipformat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/ipformat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Package written in Golang to process and format ip Addresses to and from ipv4/ipv6. Can also take ranges in cidr notation. The entire projects &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/SiloCityLabs/ipFormat&#34;&gt;source code&lt;/a&gt; is posted on github.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can include a package written for Golang projects to quickly get started with a simple function.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Golang</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/2019/06/24/getting-started-with-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/2019/06/24/getting-started-with-golang/</guid>
      <description>Go Applications A Go app can vary from 3 to millions of lines of code. They should also be written with one or multiple files with the extension .go You can use any text editor to write a Go program like nano, but our favorite and most supported is Visual Studio Code.
Setting up a Go Environment For all of our tutorials we will be using VSCode to help us ease into the language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultra minimal Raspbian Image for Pi Zero and Zero W</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/06/13/ultra-minimal-raspbian-image-for-pi-zero-and-zero-w/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 23:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/06/13/ultra-minimal-raspbian-image-for-pi-zero-and-zero-w/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to make a ultra lite image that I can quickly drop Go programs onto. This image had a few requirements, be under 300MB, have less than 20MB ram usage idle, startup in under 5 seconds. I will post below everything I did to strip this down so that it can be replicated in the future. Currently with the steps below I have achieved 427MB/16MB, close to my goal for disk and memory usage is below the goal. As for bootup time, I am limited by network connection time 5+ seconds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install a fresh Raspbian Stretch Lite image into the SD card (source).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Configure headless SSH and Wi-Fi (if necessary) before starting the SD card (source).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What can golang do?</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/06/06/what-can-golang-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/06/06/what-can-golang-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing makes a developer crazier than a new programming language, right? So, I started learning Go about 6 months ago and now I am going to share with you my reasons for doing so.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi Booting From USB on older models</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/06/01/raspberry-pi-booting-from-usb-on-older-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 03:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/06/01/raspberry-pi-booting-from-usb-on-older-models/</guid>
      <description>Booting from USB is easy on a Pi1, Pi2, or Pi3. This can be useful in mamy cases to speed up the performance of your pi when using a slow sd card. It can also provide a reliable location where you operating system data resides. Sd cards are prone to data corruption from writes a operating system ussually does.
  Write the latest Raspbian image to an SD card and boot it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbyist 3d printer roundup of 2019</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/31/hobbyist-3d-printer-roundup-of-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/31/hobbyist-3d-printer-roundup-of-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When we first entered 3d printing we started off quickly printing many and many objects. Slowly our printer started to die down once the printer began acting up. Our current printer the Robox rbx1 became the most pain in the ass printer we saw online. Everything was due to the proprietary software and the lack of 3rd party parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We started to try and simplify remote access by using Teamviewer and even went as far as to buy a CEL Root SD card. The CEL Root was even worse than our current methods. This is when we finally had it. We wanted an open source printer with a decent bed, 3rd party parts, and Octoprint support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together me and my team came up with the list of hobby printers under $2000. We&amp;rsquo;ll get a decent filament printer now and a small resin printer later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning up duplicates on NAS</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/30/cleaning-up-duplicates-on-nas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 23:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/30/cleaning-up-duplicates-on-nas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the last year me and my wife have been using the network server more frequently from its &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.silocitylabs.com/post/2019/02/21/home-server-setup/&#34;&gt;initial install and setup&lt;/a&gt;. We share 3-4 computers across the house and constantly move files onto the NAS. I have installed Nextcloud which I will detail in another post in the future. We have come across an issue that I have noticed with the network share. We moved all of our images and files over and ended up with tons of duplicates and a giant mess. I will show you what I am doing to clean that up. Our Nas is running on a ubuntu server. The following commands should work on most linux NAS servers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Server Setup.</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/30/home-server-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 23:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/30/home-server-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I will talk about my server setup by request. I setup my server originally for Security cameras because I was tired of proprietary software that every different camera has. My setup right now includes 4 entirely different types of cameras. None of them officially support ONVIF. Every one of my cameras was free so quality was not something I cared for. Today, my server now has my Windows File share (Samba), offsite Sync, Software Raid, Crontab Network Speed monitoring and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zoneminder.com/&#34;&gt;zoneminder&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axis 2130 PTZ and Zoneminder</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/02/07/axis-2130-ptz-and-zoneminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 23:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/02/07/axis-2130-ptz-and-zoneminder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;axis-2130-ptz-and-zoneminder&#34;&gt;Axis 2130 PTZ and Zoneminder&lt;/h3&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/08/41X1FB2KSBL._SY400_.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; width=&#34;429&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;h4 id=&#34;details&#34;&gt;Details:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This camera is very dated, also using a proprietary power adapter, no WiFi and very difficult to setup. Once you are on my network you have full viewing access to my camera. My router fortunately has network isolation so I am able to block access to it except via my server that has zoneminder nvr software installed. Unfortunately you will not be able to control the ptz from Zoneminder directly due to the age of the camera. But you can however give it a fixed position in the web panel it has built in. I would recommend setting its default fixed position after a reboot or power loss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Test internal WiFi</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/01/24/speed-test-internal-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/01/24/speed-test-internal-wifi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/12/speedtest.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;377&#34; width=&#34;567&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;Many have heard the term speed test, the first thing that comes to mind is speedtest.net or google&amp;rsquo;s speed test tool. Many don&amp;rsquo;t know that speed on your internal network also affects you. When testing internet speed your device sends data to router then out to the internet, what if your router is the issue. Even worse, your device. I will show u a very handy utility I use to make sure everything in my house runs great. Its called &lt;a href=&#34;https://iperf.fr/iperf-download.php&#34;&gt;iPerf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Genius WideCam 320 and Zoneminder</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/01/10/genius-widecam-320-and-zoneminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 23:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/01/10/genius-widecam-320-and-zoneminder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;genius-32200318100-widecam-320-usb-and-zoneminder&#34;&gt;Genius 32200318100 WideCam 320 USB and Zoneminder&lt;/h3&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/08/26-179-100-02.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;h4 id=&#34;details&#34;&gt;Details:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although I have this particular camera, any basic USB webcam will work the same way. The setup for this one was very simple and its the most stable camera out of my whole setup. There however is no nightvision. I counter this by trigger the lights to turn on if motion sensor is tripped.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get 400mbps for 3 years at $44.99</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/01/08/how-to-get-400mbps-for-44-99-3-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/01/08/how-to-get-400mbps-for-44-99-3-years/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the process I found while setting up a new service for my brother at his house. This will only work for new customers. The address has to have no existing connections for this to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Intro call, During this call you will call and ask about pricing to see if you are willing to activate a new service. You will need to seem uninterested and are willing to go without internet. Don&amp;rsquo;t make it brief. Keep it going to get more info. Ask about promotional pricing for 400mbps plans.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nightowl BNC and Zoneminder</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/12/27/nightowl-bnc-and-zoneminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 23:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/12/27/nightowl-bnc-and-zoneminder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;nightowl-bnc&#34;&gt;Nightowl BNC&lt;/h3&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/08/images.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;251&#34; width=&#34;201&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;h4 id=&#34;details&#34;&gt;Details:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are just about every cheap camera sold in store. You can buy these at home depot, walmart, and other retailers. Your best bet is craigslist you can get them for like $10 each. They use a basic analog signal you can hookup to a TV with the right connector. The main connector is called a BNC connector. The downside to these cameras is that they usually cap out at 720p. You will also need a PCI or usb device to hook it up to your server. Unless you already have these cameras laying around, I WOULD NOT RECOMMEND this setup for purchase. Its cheaper to get a 1080p camera on amazon for $20 with less wiring and no pci card.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Linux</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/12/18/switching-to-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/12/18/switching-to-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/12/the-best-linux-distros-for-beginners-switching-from-windows-mac-670x3353674761306310635625.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;335&#34; width=&#34;670&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;I have just about had it with Windows updates being forced on me. Graphics drivers breaking. My settings getting reset every time I get on and many &lt;a href=&#34;https://duckduckgo.com/?q=windows+updates+breaks&amp;amp;atb=v147-1__&amp;amp;t=cros&amp;amp;iar=news&amp;amp;ia=&#34;&gt;other reasons&lt;/a&gt; I won&amp;rsquo;t begin to rant about. I chose to go with a decently common operating system for better compatibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have gone through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://linuxhint.com/rufus_bootable_usb_install_ubuntu_18-04_lts/&#34;&gt;install process and have installed Ubuntu 18.04LTS&lt;/a&gt;. For less advanced Linux users you can go with a simpler Linux like &lt;a href=&#34;https://linoxide.com/distros/install-solus-usb/&#34;&gt;Solus&lt;/a&gt; which is a little more GUI friendly system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can modify ubuntu to your likings using a tool called &amp;ldquo;gnome tweaks&amp;rdquo; and you can disable animations to speed things up by using a tool called &amp;ldquo;dconf-editor&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In dconf-editor, browse to &lt;strong&gt;org.gnome.desktop.interface&lt;/strong&gt; and set &lt;strong&gt;enable-animations=false&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also run this command to disable animations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gsettings set org.gnome.desktop.interface enable-animations false&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You do not need to log out and back in, it should take effect immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After getting all settled and having all my software carried over. I had a few pieces of software that was not compatible and I still needed. Most of my software was available in Ubuntu application store. Everything left is listed below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://google.com/chrome&#34;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://store.steampowered.com/about/&#34;&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git -&amp;gt; installed from terminal &amp;ldquo;sudo apt install git&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://thishosting.rocks/install-java-ubuntu/&#34;&gt;Java 10 (64-bit) -&amp;gt; installed from terminal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://amd.com&#34;&gt;AMD Driver&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://steamcommunity.com/games/221410/announcements/detail/1696055855739350561&#34;&gt;PC Games, Steam Beta Proton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SketchUp 2016 -&amp;gt; Windows VM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pcsteps.com/5110-install-origin-linux-mint-ubuntu-wine/&#34;&gt;Origin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;H&amp;amp;R Block Premium + Efile + State -&amp;gt; Windows VM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft office -&amp;gt; libreoffice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu &lt;a href=&#34;https://vitux.com/add-new-document-back-to-the-right-click-menu-in-ubuntu-18-04/&#34;&gt;Get right click new documents back&lt;/a&gt;. Here is a link to a couple of &lt;a href=&#34;https://downloads.techreanimate.com/mprryu&#34;&gt;templates&lt;/a&gt; we made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get the Windows-only software running I installed Virtualbox and installed Windows 10 and started to hack away at all its imperfections to slim it down. This virtual machine won&amp;rsquo;t be used that often so its a compromise I&amp;rsquo;m willing to make. I can also set quick one click restore points just in case windows breaks. I have compiled a list for all to use:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSCM-13101B and Zoneminder</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/12/13/rscm-13101b-and-zoneminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 23:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/12/13/rscm-13101b-and-zoneminder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;rosewill-shieldeye-rscm-13101b-and-zoneminder&#34;&gt;Rosewill SHIELDeye RSCM-13101B and Zoneminder&lt;/h3&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/08/81-147-048-Z01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;h4 id=&#34;details&#34;&gt;Details:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This camera is not listed as officially supporting ONVIF, but it does have it. It barely works so I had to do a workaround to add it in. This camera is a OEM camera, Rosewill just re-branded them. Other models that will most likely work the same way. RSCM-13702B RSCM-13702W RSCM-13101B RSCM-15702 RSCM-121001W&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BV Tech 4MP 2K H.265 IP67 and Zoneminder</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/11/28/bv-tech-4mp-2k-h-265-ip67-and-zoneminder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 23:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/11/28/bv-tech-4mp-2k-h-265-ip67-and-zoneminder/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/11/61qmqoijgvl._sl1000_.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;1000&#34; width=&#34;1000&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;Model: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bvsecurity.com/index.php/ca-ipbf-4mp-wifi.html&#34;&gt;ca-ipbf-4mp-wifi-fba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This problem gave me a few issues I will go over briefly. This was fairly simple once I realized what I was doing wrong. I originally had it plugged in via an Ethernet cable to setup to WiFi like most cameras. But this camera actually just uses the microphone to transmit settings. Once I removed the Ethernet cable everything worked fine. I actually snipped off the Ethernet knowing I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t need it, saving space with the clunky cable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Backups without the cloud</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/11/23/secure-backups-without-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 17:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/11/23/secure-backups-without-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/11/22-501-073_R01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ioSafe SOLO G3 4TB USB 3.0&#34; height=&#34;960&#34; width=&#34;1280&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;I accidentally stumbled upon this solution while trying to find cloud providers to backup my 2TB&amp;rsquo;s worth of NAS backups. With every single cloud solution being out of price range for the size data I needed I had to look elsewhere. I came across the ioSafe Solo G3 enclosure. It boasts about being safe in every way possible, Fire Proof, Water Proof, and Theft Proof. I almost considered it too good to be true, seemed legit enough after watching some YouTube videos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall mounted Google home free</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/10/27/wall-mounted-google-home-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 03:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/10/27/wall-mounted-google-home-free/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wanted to wall mount my google home mini for the kitchen since there is not really a nice place to set it down. I also didnt want to pay for a mount or 3d print anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can use zip ties or bread bag ties to secure the cable in a loop like below.&lt;/p&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/10/20181027_2304361152181891921713046.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;1920&#34; width=&#34;1439&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;After u have the 3 ties in place. Just plug it in and you should be set.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12v circuit for battery backup</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/10/11/12v-circuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/10/11/12v-circuit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My goal is to eventually run everything off a battery backup circuit. Most common systems run on a 12v battery. To start im start off with a few basic things and getting everything running from 12v.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Items needed:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12v power supply&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12v to 5v dc to dc step down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This controller came with a few negatives right off the jump. I dont want to link to a bad controller but ill still describe what I did.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infinite, Free?, Small storage for electronics</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/09/18/infinite-free-small-storage-for-electronics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/09/18/infinite-free-small-storage-for-electronics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/09/20180917_2019313975750998363509017.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;1440&#34; width=&#34;1920&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;Im a little dissapointed in myself for not thinking of it sooner. I tossed about 20 of these in the recycling bin before I realized I could reuse them myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Title is a little deceptive yes, but I still consider them free when you have a source. Baby formula containers!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup home internet</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/09/15/backup-home-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/09/15/backup-home-internet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With new most asus routers you can use a feature called dual wan. I have the luxury of having a work provided cell phone I am using for this. Before having that I had a free service called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.freedompop.com/phone&#34;&gt;freedompop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use cases (mainly mine):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Watching netflix withouth interuptions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Backup internet for home security system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anything internet&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To start off we plugin a cell phone to the routers usb port.&lt;/p&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/09/20180915_0932318158192643190909326.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;1440&#34; width=&#34;1920&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reusing Tile as car tracker.</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/07/19/reusing-tile-as-car-tracker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 06:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/07/19/reusing-tile-as-car-tracker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever since I switched to Samsung smart things I purchased presence sensors and had no more use for my tiles after the batteries died. I retired them to a box for a long time. Today I figured out a neat project for the tile. I am going to turn it into a tracker for my cars. This is not real time tracking but can help find your car in larger cities.&lt;/p&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/07/use-your-phone-to-find-your-car3939281002465595095.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;231&#34; width=&#34;231&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;Supplies/Tools needed:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pry Tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hot Glue gun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Voltage Meter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dead battery Tile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://a.tra.li/Tn1h&#34;&gt;DC to DC Buck Converter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://a.tra.li/Tqhy&#34;&gt;Linear converter&lt;/a&gt; (see update below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soldering iron&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wire stripper/cutter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drill (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3d Printer Filament box done quick</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/04/13/3d-printer-filament-box-done-quick/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 23:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/04/13/3d-printer-filament-box-done-quick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Keep your filament dry! Filament used for 3d printers will absorb moisture from the air and damp filament prints very poorly. With Buffalo&amp;rsquo;s high humidity and our printer being run in a basement, we absolutely need a dry box for our spools. We ordered parts ahead of time, slammed this box together in an afternoon, and then baked our spools to rid them of moisture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re using a large plastic bin for storage, teflon tubing to run from the box to the printer, and pneumatic connectors to ensure the filament feeds smoothly into the tubing without snagging. A large pack of silica gel keeps the box dry over time. Our basement also has an additional air dehumidifier that we keep at 50% to prevent mold growing on our wood/mdf surfaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplies:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sterilite Air Tight Bin, fits about 8-10 reels. (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00KL7VQ7S/&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-10 Meters of PTFE Teflon Tube OD 4mm ID 2mm (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B019PZ5MY4/&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;M5 Lock Nuts, 1 per reel (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07BCZ24DM/&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5mm Male Thread 4mm Push in Joint Pneumatic Connector, 2x per reel (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B009ITFXDI/&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scrap Wood Strip&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;608ZZ Bearings, 4x per reel (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00NX3LKY6/&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DRY&amp;amp;DRY Silica Gel Desiccant Packet, Rechargeable (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B06XKMV1HV/&#34;&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tools:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Power Drill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5mm or 3/16&amp;rdquo; Drill Bit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4&amp;rdquo; Drill bit or larger&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sander/Sandpaper (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rubber Mallet, Optional but makes it easier to fit bearings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3D Prints&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Filament Spool Roller - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:2185015&#34;&gt;https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:2185015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android - BN Blitz</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-bn-blitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-bn-blitz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Built from scratch and a team of 1. This app integrates build types and flavours to quickly create another version of the application. The code base for both &lt;a href=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-buffalonews&#34;&gt;The Buffalo News&lt;/a&gt; and BN Blitz app are one in the same with simple changes that change how they work in a single config file. This was designed to be allowed to integrate into wordpress api and resold to other news orginizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The News’ team has you covered, from training camp to the draft – and every snap in between. Mark Gaughan, Jerry Sullivan, Tim Graham and Jay Skurski lead the coverage with breaking updates and in-depth analysis through daily blogs posts, stories and columns. Plus, video reports and exclusive photos from every game. On game day, get real-time reports from The News’ writers at the game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android - BN Hockey</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-bnhockey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-bnhockey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This application incorporates a Android Webview for display the website as an application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The News’ team has you covered, from preseason to the draft – and every puck drop in between. John Vogl, Mike Harrington, Amy Moritz, Bucky Gleason and Jerry Sullivan lead the coverage with breaking news updates and in-depth analysis through daily blog posts, articles and columns. Plus, video reports and exclusive photos from every game. On game nights, get real-time reports from The News’ writers at the rink.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And The News’ coverage goes beyond Pegulaville. From the Cup final to the Scouting Combine, The News’ writers are on the ground at the biggest events of the year to take you inside what’s happening with your team and the league.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This app presents all of The Buffalo News’ coverage of the Sabres and league in a format that is optimized for fans on the go. In addition to current articles and blog updates, you will have access to photo galleries, stats and the best of The News’ Sabres archive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The depth of The News’ staff is unmatched. John Vogl has been covering the Sabres since 2002-03. The award-winning writer is the Buffalo chapter chairman for the Professional Hockey Writers’ Association. Mike Harrington, a Canisius College graduate who began his career as a News reporter in 1987, has been covering the Sabres since 2007. He is a member of the Professional Hockey Writers&amp;rsquo; Association. Amy Moritz, a native of Lockport, joined The News&amp;rsquo; Sabres beat in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android - Buffalo News Addon</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-buffalonews-addon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-buffalonews-addon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Built from scratch and a team of 1. You can read paper copies of The Buffalo News through our Addon application that integrates seamlessly with the main application. The applications have internal authentication that happens between applications. The user does not even know he is bouncing between applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android - The Buffalo News</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-buffalonews/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-buffalonews/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Built from scratch and a team of 1. Get the latest local news, sports and weather wherever you go with The Buffalo News Android Mobile application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buffalo News makes viewing and sharing the news easy. With a few clicks, you can read and watch the latest news or share it with family and friends by e-mail or post to Twitter and Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it&amp;rsquo;s severe weather, breaking news or sports scores and entertainment news, The Buffalo News application keeps you in-the-know while you&amp;rsquo;re on-the-go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also read paper copies of The Buffalo News through our &lt;a href=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/android-buffalonews-addon&#34;&gt;Addon application&lt;/a&gt; that integrates seamlessly with the main application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing DNS settings for Android Development</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/03/02/changing-dns-settings-for-android-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 16:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/03/02/changing-dns-settings-for-android-development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2018/03/ezgif-1-6db60a8e39-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;395&#34; width=&#34;728&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This relates to any similar development environment. This guide will help you setup your device to work for your development setup either locally or a remote server. No root required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I will describe the use case scenario where this is useful:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>433MHZ More Things for Smart Things</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/02/05/433mhz-more-things-for-smart-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 22:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/02/05/433mhz-more-things-for-smart-things/</guid>
      <description>Finally - off the breadboard and into a working environment. It&amp;rsquo;s currently working for 433mhz sensors, I will possibly be adding more frequencies later. For now I will continue refining the code to release it on github.
   Day 1:
A few issues. I accidentally flipped the polarities on the siren. I will eventually implement a 12v regulator to up the voltage for the siren for the full 120db power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual AC Router Setup for $120</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/02/02/dual-ac-router-setup-for-120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 19:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/02/02/dual-ac-router-setup-for-120/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I will be using two &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/01/flashing-merlin-to-tm-ac1900-or-ac68u/&#34;&gt;Custom firmware&lt;/a&gt; routers to get full house coverage on a very old house with thick lead filled walls. The entire project took 6 hours due to some unexpected issues we faced. You can flash any device below as well to &lt;a href=&#34;https://asuswrt.lostrealm.ca/&#34;&gt;Merlin custom firmware&lt;/a&gt; but its entirely optional. This will work with the stock firmware.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>433mhz testing</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/19/433mhz-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 14:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/19/433mhz-testing/</guid>
      <description>I decided due to the lack of community support I am not going to make a Zigbee 433mhz chip instead I will continue my efforts with the WiFi esp8266. Now that I have the 433mhz working with the esp8266 I will be performing some distance testing with a few receivers I purchased and different antennas I have.
     Update to: https://blog.silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/01/smart-things-433mhz/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashing Merlin to TM-AC1900 or AC68U (Updated for 384 builds)</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/01/flashing-merlin-to-tm-ac1900-or-ac68u/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 03:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/01/flashing-merlin-to-tm-ac1900-or-ac68u/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Very few people know that you can save yourself some money by buying a &lt;a href=&#34;http://a.tra.li/Smz7&#34;&gt;T-mobile router on Amazon&lt;/a&gt;. Downside is having to flash it to have the latest firmware free of vulnerabilities. In this guide I will show you how to flash a TM-AC1900 to a RT-AC68U then into merlin custom firmware. I have tested it myself and can confirm that it works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Update: Asus began rolling back firmware on the stock setups. They are not providing Merlin with the source for Ai-Mesh so you need to be on stock to use it. I have updated the guide to provide instructions on how to prevent the rollback from happening. You can also use this guide to recover from a rollback.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Smart Home Setup</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/28/complete-smart-home-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 18:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/28/complete-smart-home-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/smart-home-2769210_960_720-e1514497002881.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;446&#34; width=&#34;907&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to talk about my smart home setup from the ground up. I have many articles describing my setup in pieces but not everyone gets an entire overview of everything I have setup here. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a mansion or anything fancy like built in sprinkler/irrigation, so this will be more catered to your average city home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Assistant&lt;/strong&gt;:
r
Google Home and/or Mini manage my random routines that aren&amp;rsquo;t part of a automation rule. Going to the basement to do laundry, or going to sleep at random times. I can just send a command and google home will handle it. Link your SmartThings account and Google Home together for best results. Give all your devices aliases to make it easier to command via Google. I want one located in every central room of the house, Kitchen, Living room, Master Bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/100417-google-home-mini7347-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; height=&#34;467&#34; width=&#34;830&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Control Center&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What controls my entire setup and why I chose this hub vs others. My only hub is a &lt;strong&gt;Samsung SmartThings hub&lt;/strong&gt;. This manages just about everything in my home minus the security cameras. I did heavy research on many hubs including Wink, IOT (hub-less), and Phillips hue. Why SmartThings?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartThings zigbee vs Dome light cover</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/26/smartthings-zigbee-vs-dome-light-cover/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 17:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/26/smartthings-zigbee-vs-dome-light-cover/</guid>
      <description>For Christmas my mother got a full smart home kit. Samsung SmartThings, sengled bulbs, google home. After pluging everything in the hub was having issues. Finding all bulbs in dome covers. I removed the glass from the dome cover and tried again with no luck. Afterwards I removed the bulb from the socket and put it in a lamp. Detected and added to smartthings fine in the lamp. Readded it to the dome cover and it works now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartThings &#43; Vision Micro Switch [Update]</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/18/smartthings-vision-micro-switch-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 20:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/18/smartthings-vision-micro-switch-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How to get a cheap smart home that actually works. Vision Micro switches lets you use the old fashion switch and also continue to use your old bulbs. Instead of paying $10-30 per smart bulb, you pay around $25 for a single or $30 for a 2 relay switch. 2 relay switches help you save a ton more money, you can use one for 2 gang boxes saving you 2x more money ($15/switch). If you think about it, most ceiling lights have 2-3 bulbs, Why buy so many bulbs when you can buy a single switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/397hvxAjlj4&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SmartThings &#43; Vision Micro Switch</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/smartthings-vision-micro-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 19:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/smartthings-vision-micro-switch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have found a neat little alternative to full price switches online. I gave myself a budget of $20 per wall switch for the house and until I found something around that I was not gonna buy any. I just think that $50 for a wall switch is a little ridiculous in my opinion. These switches are still over my max budget but at least I found a reason for one of the partners here to buy it instead [&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.silocitylabs.com/post/author/bana0615/&#34;&gt;bana0615&lt;/a&gt;]. He has a double switch in his house and they do not sell double smart switches anywhere. This micro controller solves his problem. The double switch relays will put me under budget for some locations in the house though with the ability to work for two switches at once.&lt;/p&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/419E0PAR7HL.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Double Toggle Switch&#34; height=&#34;500&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New generators coming soon</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/new-generators-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 01:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/new-generators-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Cant wait to show you what we have in store, new generators coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New print bed</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/ebay-print-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 01:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/15/ebay-print-bed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We received our new print bed from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ebay.com/itm/192342007627&#34;&gt;eBay/China&lt;/a&gt;. Not a Lokbuild but at least its cheaper. First thing I noticed is that this sheet is thicker than a Lokbuild, 0.6mm thick instead of 0.5. When I followed the steps on calibrating I clicked &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;6&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; 8 times to ensure proper spacing instead of the original 4.&lt;/p&gt;






    
        &lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2017/12/img_20171106_1706507253338128094262765.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Before applying pad&#34; height=&#34;1280&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robox Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Launch AutoMaker software and navigate to Calibration button&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow instructions until asked to insert paper between nozzles and build plate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow instructions and raise nozzles to point at which paper moves freely between nozzles and build plate&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set height &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;4&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;6&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; 8 clicks higher than this point (i.e. 0.4 mm)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proceed as normal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated water system?</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/06/automated-water-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 20:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/06/automated-water-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A friend at work asked if I could help solve his issues with his water intake from the well. At first I was like um why? Living in the city I did not know anything about how country side water systems worked. Water pumped from a well has a chance that it may contain too much sulfur making the water smell. He wanted to pull rain water into a tank and use it as primary with the well water as a failsafe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am thinking about using a basic ESP8266 along with a couple of water pressure sensors and relays triggering the water pumps he already has. The code should be very simple to write and I already have most of the hardware here minus the sensor.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phillips hue &#43; smartthings</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/04/phillips-hue-smartthings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 19:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/04/phillips-hue-smartthings/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure why it started working all of a sudden. I&amp;rsquo;m glad I did not buy a Hue hub. I had a test bulb plugged in as a normal bulb when it randomly showed up to my SmartThings hub. This happened after adding Sengled classic bulbs to my system and a SmartThings hub update. I think maybe it had to do with Zigbee adding cross compatibility between ZLL and ZHA protocols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Things 433mhz</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/01/smart-things-433mhz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 01:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/01/smart-things-433mhz/</guid>
      <description>Going to be creating a receiver to translate 433mhz sensors to smart things, Most likely going to be using a esp8266 to make it easier to configure. I still have to figure out how to identify the smart things hub withouth manually entering in its ip, maybe upnp?
I also bought a CC2530 chip for zigbee testing, Not sure what im going to do with that yet.
 Edit: I think I may have made a mistake buying zigbee chips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATTO.com Domain Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com-acquisition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com-acquisition/</guid>
      <description>After hearing that they have been trying to contact a company for the purchase of atto.com for 16 years, I figured I could give it a shot. I helped ATTO Technology locate the correct point of contact in a +10000 employee company to initiate negotiations of the acquisition for the 4 letter domain name. We acquired the Domain name by the end of July.
You can checkout the other contributors for refferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATTO Technology SEO Redesign</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was hired for this company to perform SEO, shortly after google had scheduled the release of a new search algorithm that would reduce views on pages that were not mobile complaint. ATTO got the effect of this with a 50% drop in traffic in a matter of days. A website with over a million views a month it needed to be overhauled. I was tasked with a complete redesign on the website and its 800+ pages. I monitored and improved SEO on the pages over time as well as slowly gained back that 50% loss in traffic. You can checkout the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ldrrp/detail/project/945228877/contributors/&#34;&gt;other contributors&lt;/a&gt; for refferences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RDNS XSS On Industry Standard Looking Glass</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/lg-xss-cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/lg-xss-cve/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My commitment to security is always a goal of mine. The &amp;lsquo;industry standard&amp;rsquo; network looking glass now faces a pretty nasty XSS vulnerability which is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/telephone/LookingGlass/tree/4367733198698c4d314c51731e0b480b7d0383b3&#34;&gt;listed on github&lt;/a&gt; and I discovered. An RDNS XSS was disclosed which has been patched by a temporary fix I applied to it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClouDNS API Library</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/cloudns-api-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/cloudns-api-php/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a wrapper library for the ClouDNS API to be used by PHP applications. It tries to ease the integration of the API into your applications by handling all interactions with API and providing a simple interface to interact with. The entire projects &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/silo-city-labs-llc/cloudns-api-php&#34;&gt;source code&lt;/a&gt; is posted on gitlab.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>