<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>php on SCL Blog</title>
    <link>https://silocitylabs.com/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in php on SCL Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 22:36:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://silocitylabs.com/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalonews.com</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/buffalonews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/buffalonews/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;During my time working for the buffalo news I made many changes to the website. I handled and wrote the mobile api for applications to pull data for the website. I also made visual changes on the website including new styles, layout changes and more. I assisted staff on making changes required in a fashionable time. Other tasks included following up with customers about specific issues for troubleshooting. We used php as the main language for a system powered by wordpress. Also optimized and wrote code for wordpress plugins and other integrations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COD Random Class Generator</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/codrcg-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/codrcg-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COD RCG is a random class generator that random generates classes for anyone who plays call of duty to enjoy. This provides new enjoyment for the game e.g. it may choose a gun the player has never used.  It also brings more challenge because you never know what you’re going to get as a class, it could be good or it could put you at a huge disadvantage, but that’s where the fun comes in trying to win and do well in the game when you’re using this crazy class that you normally would not. We launched this website less than a week after call of duty came out. I created my own algorithms to randomly create a class based on the “create a class” system used in Call of Duty. It was a challenge because there are tons of possible class possibilities that can be created. So once I finished that I then had to go and make sure all the gun, attachment, camos, equipment, perks and score streaks were all named correctly. This site and app has been pretty popular with over 25,000,000 views and over 5,000,000 classes generated. The Android app has over 50k installs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codrcg.com&#34;&gt;Website Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.techreanimate.blackops3&#34;&gt;Android App Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zips Wiseguys Pizzeria Website</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/wise-guys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/wise-guys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This restaurant has had multiple locations open all under one new mobile compliant website.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colocrossing Client and Admin control panel</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/colocrossing-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/colocrossing-panel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A highly advanced control panel that manages multiple datacenters across the country. This control panel has management features such as users, switches, routers, virtual machines, DDOS mitigation, port monitoring, billing, support tickets, sales and many more things. The panel grew more and more everyday become fully automated in every aspect of a datacenter technicians work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ATTO Technology SEO Redesign</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/atto-com/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was hired for this company to perform SEO, shortly after google had scheduled the release of a new search algorithm that would reduce views on pages that were not mobile complaint. ATTO got the effect of this with a 50% drop in traffic in a matter of days. A website with over a million views a month it needed to be overhauled. I was tasked with a complete redesign on the website and its 800+ pages. I monitored and improved SEO on the pages over time as well as slowly gained back that 50% loss in traffic. You can checkout the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ldrrp/detail/project/945228877/contributors/&#34;&gt;other contributors&lt;/a&gt; for refferences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Megatouchmods.com</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/megatouchmods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/megatouchmods/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A website designed to host documentation for an arcade company that went bankrupt. I manage and run this website on my own, Open source the website on github using github actions to automatically build and deploy changes made to the repository.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://megatouchmods.com&#34;&gt;megatouchmods.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/SiloCityLabs/megatouchmods.com&#34;&gt;github source code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP JSON HTML Minify</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/php-json-html-minify/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/php-json-html-minify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Both of these functions are designed to be used with ob_start() and process the output before its sent to the user. You can also include caching into this to reduce overhead for static pages. It takes the output of the page and makes the content up to 50% smaller in size by removing unused comments and whitespace in code. &lt;a href=&#34;https://downloads.techreanimate.com/auowdk&#34;&gt;Download the file here&lt;/a&gt; or look at the code below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP Mysqli DB Class</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/db-class-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/db-class-php/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A class written to simplify the use of mysqli in php. Uses similar concepts to other db classes built into other frameworks. &lt;a href=&#34;https://downloads.techreanimate.com/auowdk&#34;&gt;Download the file here&lt;/a&gt; or look at the code below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixelmon</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/pixelmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/pixelmon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/luis-portfolio/pixelmon.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Pixelmon Mod&#34; height=&#34;994&#34; width=&#34;1920&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;
    

&lt;p&gt;In my time working with Pixelmon team I played a role of working with multiple parts of the team due to my vast experience developing. Pixelmon was a hybrid game mode with minecraft and pokemon mixed in an open world game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately the game faced some pushback including dmca takedown notice from Nintendo themselves which resulted in all development ending. The game had user created content that was similar to the real game pokemon but created by hand as to avoid copyright infringement. It seems that Nintendo still carried on with the takedown however.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sending SMS via the Nexmo SMS gateway.</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/nexmo-php-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/nexmo-php-class/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A class written to simplify the use of the nexmo api gateway for SMS messaging. This class was a fork from another repository with new gateway endpoints added and adding an entirely new service for automated phone calls with a tts engine. &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/silo-city-labs-llc/Nexmo-PHP-lib&#34;&gt;Download the file here&lt;/a&gt; or look at the code below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RDNS XSS On Industry Standard Looking Glass</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/lg-xss-cve/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/lg-xss-cve/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My commitment to security is always a goal of mine. The &amp;lsquo;industry standard&amp;rsquo; network looking glass now faces a pretty nasty XSS vulnerability which is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/telephone/LookingGlass/tree/4367733198698c4d314c51731e0b480b7d0383b3&#34;&gt;listed on github&lt;/a&gt; and I discovered. An RDNS XSS was disclosed which has been patched by a temporary fix I applied to it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClouDNS API Library</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/cloudns-api-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/projects/cloudns-api-php/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a wrapper library for the ClouDNS API to be used by PHP applications. It tries to ease the integration of the API into your applications by handling all interactions with API and providing a simple interface to interact with. The entire projects &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/silo-city-labs-llc/cloudns-api-php&#34;&gt;source code&lt;/a&gt; is posted on gitlab.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>