<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on SCL Blog</title>
    <link>https://silocitylabs.com/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on SCL Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://silocitylabs.com/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PandaPaper turns malicious</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2025/paperpanda-malicious/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2025/paperpanda-malicious/</guid>
      <description>&lt;amp-img src=&#34;https://silocitylabs.com/uploads/2025/paperpanda-dead.webp&#34; alt=&#34;paper panda logo with X for eyes&#34; height=&#34;573&#34; width=&#34;1056&#34; layout=&#34;responsive&#34;&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt;&#xA;    &#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &amp;ldquo;paywalling&amp;rdquo; of scientific research papers is an ongoing problem that hinders learning, hinders scientific research, and leaches profit from publicly-funded research. PaperPanda is a Chrome extension to download academic papers. Its intention is to find free links for published papers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However what PaperPanda does under-the-hood tells another story. I&amp;rsquo;ve unearthed malicious code in PaperPanda&amp;rsquo;s Chrome extension and attempts to hide said malicious activity. This extension tried to modify my Amazon pages for unknown reasons - possibly a phisher or credit-card stealer. If you have this extension &lt;em&gt;UNINSTALL IT&lt;/em&gt;. In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how this extension is malicious and how it hides that behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Server Setup.</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/30/home-server-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 23:30:33 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2019/05/30/home-server-setup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I will talk about my server setup by request. I setup my server originally for Security cameras because I was tired of proprietary software that every different camera has. My setup right now includes 4 entirely different types of cameras. None of them officially support ONVIF. Every one of my cameras was free so quality was not something I cared for. Today, my server now has my Windows File share (Samba), offsite Sync, Software Raid, Crontab Network Speed monitoring and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zoneminder.com/&#34;&gt;zoneminder&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>433mhz testing</title>
      <link>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/19/433mhz-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 14:43:55 +0000</pubDate><author>team@silocitylabs.com (Silo City Labs LLC)</author>
      <guid>https://silocitylabs.com/post/2018/01/19/433mhz-testing/</guid>
      <description>I decided due to the lack of community support I am not going to make a Zigbee 433mhz chip instead I will continue my efforts with the WiFi esp8266. Now that I have the 433mhz working with the esp8266 I will be performing some distance testing with a few receivers I purchased and different antennas I have.&#xA;Update to: https://blog.silocitylabs.com/post/2017/12/01/smart-things-433mhz/</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
